{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"660","name":"Telway System","address":"6820 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821","owner":"Earl Owens","licenseNumber":"034588","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.12787,42.33139","geojson":{"id":"660","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.127872096,42.3313909400001]},"properties":{"name":"Telway System","owner":"Earl Owens","address":"6820 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"034588","establishmentid":"660","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1375","name":"McDonald's #7453","address":"6876 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"434","name":"Dairy Queen #10216","address":"6677 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"2953","name":"The Sting","address":"6609 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"515","name":"Holy Cross Council 2739","address":"4381 Larkins","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"950","name":"Kwong Village Chinese American","address":"6600 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"716","name":"Jordans Family Restaurant","address":"7031 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"4966","name":"Rincon Tropical","address":"6538 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"2070","name":"Cesar Chavez Academy","address":"4100 Martin St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"1013","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #302","address":"7060 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3288","name":"Los Dos Amigos-1","address":"7115 Parkwood St","zipcode":"4821"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44874","inspectionDate":"2019-01-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"Under the Shelves","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"43880","inspectionDate":"2018-09-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"43206","inspectionDate":"2018-06-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-602.11","violationDescription":"(A)  FOOD PACKAGED in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, shall be labeled as specified in LAW. \r\n(B) The name of the FOOD source for each MAJOR FOOD ALLERGEN contained in the FOOD unless the FOOD source is already part of the common or usual name of the respective ingredient. (Pf)\r\n(C)  Bulk FOOD that is available for CONSUMER self-dispensing shall be prominently labeled with the following information in plain view of the CONSUMER:\r\n(1)  the manufacturer's or processor's label that was provided with the  FOOD; or \r\n(2)  A card, sign, or other method of notification that includes the information required by law. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Packaged food label(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Serving area","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \r\n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\r\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\r\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\r\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on","subProblem":"Counter","location":"COUNTER","subLocation":"In the Front counter","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store wiping cloths completely submersed in sanitizer."},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"light shield(s)","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"and the Fryer(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"Under the Shelves","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"and the Prep area","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."}]},{"inspectionid":"40423","inspectionDate":"2017-09-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above.e"},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"In the Back Room","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-602.11","violationDescription":"(A)  FOOD PACKAGED in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, shall be labeled as specified in LAW. \r\n(B) The name of the FOOD source for each MAJOR FOOD ALLERGEN contained in the FOOD unless the FOOD source is already part of the common or usual name of the respective ingredient. (Pf)\r\n(C)  Bulk FOOD that is available for CONSUMER self-dispensing shall be prominently labeled with the following information in plain view of the CONSUMER:\r\n(1)  the manufacturer's or processor's label that was provided with the  FOOD; or \r\n(2)  A card, sign, or other method of notification that includes the information required by law. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Packaged food label(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE STATION","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-301.12","violationDescription":"(A) Except as specified in ¶ (C) of this section, a sink with at least 3 compartments shall be provided for manually washing, rinsing, and SANITIZING EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS. (Pf)   \r\n(B) Sink compartments shall be large enough to accommodate immersion of the largest EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS. If EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS are too large for the WAREWASHING sink, a WAREWASHING machine or alternative EQUIPMENT as specified in ¶ (C) of this section shall be used. (Pf)\r\n(C) Before a 2-compartment sink is used the PERMIT HOLDER shall have its use APPROVED.\r\n(D) A 2-compartment sink may not be used for WAREWASHING operations where cleaning and SANITIZING solutions are used for a continuous or intermittent flow of KITCHENWARE or TABLEWARE in an ongoing WAREWASHING process.\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Three compartment sink","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"Dishwashing","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \r\n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\r\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\r\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\r\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on","subProblem":"Counter","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store wiping cloths completely submersed in sanitizer."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"and the Cookline","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]},{"inspectionid":"38109","inspectionDate":"2017-02-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER BUCKETS","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"violationCode":"3-602.11","violationDescription":"(A)  FOOD PACKAGED in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, shall be labeled as specified in LAW. \r\n(B) The name of the FOOD source for each MAJOR FOOD ALLERGEN contained in the FOOD unless the FOOD source is already part of the common or usual name of the respective ingredient. (Pf)\r\n(C)  Bulk FOOD that is available for CONSUMER self-dispensing shall be prominently labeled with the following information in plain view of the CONSUMER:\r\n(1)  the manufacturer's or processor's label that was provided with the  FOOD; or \r\n(2)  A card, sign, or other method of notification that includes the information required by law. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not include","subProblem":"List of ingredients","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"A certified manager shall be at the facility during operational hours."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]},{"inspectionid":"36181","inspectionDate":"2016-08-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Single-service/use items","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate separation to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"3-602.11","violationDescription":"(A)  FOOD PACKAGED in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, shall be labeled as specified in LAW. \r\n(B) The name of the FOOD source for each MAJOR FOOD ALLERGEN contained in the FOOD unless the FOOD source is already part of the common or usual name of the respective ingredient. (Pf)\r\n(C)  Bulk FOOD that is available for CONSUMER self-dispensing shall be prominently labeled with the following information in plain view of the CONSUMER:\r\n(1)  the manufacturer's or processor's label that was provided with the  FOOD; or \r\n(2)  A card, sign, or other method of notification that includes the information required by law. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food label(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \r\n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\r\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\r\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\r\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not completely submerged in sanitizing solution","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Submerge wiping cloths in sanitizer between use"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"660"}}